<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Mpeg7 xmlns="urn:mpeg:mpeg7:schema:2001" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <DescriptionMetadata>
        <Version>5.0</Version>
        <Comment>
            <FreeTextAnnotation />
        </Comment>
        <Creator>
            <Role href="creatorCS">
                <Name>Creator</Name>
            </Role>
            <Agent xsi:type="PersonType">
                <Name>
                    <FamilyName>Olav</FamilyName>
                    <GivenName>Løne</GivenName> 
                </Name>
            </Agent>
        </Creator>
        <CreationTime>2012-04-19T17:13</CreationTime>
        <Instrument>
            <Tool>
                <Name>Aardvark v0.56</Name>
            </Tool>
        </Instrument>
    </DescriptionMetadata>
    <Description xsi:type="ContentEntityType">
        <MultimediaContent xsi:type="ImageType">
            <Image>
                <MediaInformation>
                    <MediaProfile master="true">
                        <MediaFormat>
                            <Content href="image" />
                            <FileFormat href="urn:mpeg:MPEG7FileFormatCS:1">
                                <Name>JPEG</Name>
                            </FileFormat>
                            <VisualCoding>
                                <Format href="urn:mpeg:MPEG7FileFormatCS:1" colorDomain="color">
                                    <Name>JPEG</Name>
                                </Format>
                                <Pixel bitsPer="24" />
                                <Frame width="2592" height="1944" />
                            </VisualCoding>
                        </MediaFormat>
                        <MediaInstance>
                            <InstanceIdentifier />
                            <MediaLocator>
                                <MediaUri>C:\Users\Olav\Documents\Oppgaave\Bilete\In the Conservatory.jpg</MediaUri>
                            </MediaLocator>
                        </MediaInstance>
                    </MediaProfile>
                    <MediaProfile>
                        <MediaFormat>
                            <Content href="image" />
                            <FileFormat href="urn:mpeg:MPEG7FileFormatCS:1">
                                <Name>JPEG</Name>
                            </FileFormat>
                            <VisualCoding>
                                <Format href="urn:mpeg:MPEG7FileFormatCS:1" colorDomain="color">
                                    <Name>JPEG</Name>
                                </Format>
                                <Pixel bitsPer="24" />
                                <Frame width="120" height="120" />
                            </VisualCoding>
                        </MediaFormat>
                        <MediaInstance>
                            <InstanceIdentifier />
                            <MediaLocator>
                                <MediaUri>C:\Users\Olav\Documents\Oppgaave\Bilete\In the Conservatory.jpg</MediaUri>
                            </MediaLocator>
                        </MediaInstance>
                    </MediaProfile>
                </MediaInformation>
                <CreationInformation>
                    <Creation>
                        <Title>Creation information</Title>
                        <Creator>
                            <Role href="creatorCS">
                                <Name>Creator</Name>
                            </Role>
                            <Agent xsi:type="PersonType">
                                <Name>
                                    <FamilyName>Manet</FamilyName>
                                    <GivenName>Edouard</GivenName>
                                </Name>
                            </Agent>
                        </Creator>
                        <CreationCoordinates>
                            <Date>
                                <TimePoint>2008-05-28T22:02:13</TimePoint>
                            </Date>
                        </CreationCoordinates>
                        </Creation>
                    </CreationInformation>  
                    <TextAnnotation>
                        <FreeTextAnnotation>
                            Manet preferred compositions with two figures as opposed to the straightforward portrait 
                            form because it opened up the possibility of interesting dialogue situations. The double 
                            portrait of Jules Guillemet and his wife, painted in the conservatory of the painter 
                            Johann Georges Otto Rosen, is one of the most important of these works because of the 
                            sensitivity with which it uses the most delicate nuances of colours and contrasts to 
                            describe and re-connect the psychologically tense, only outwardly detached, relationship 
                            of the two figures. The theme of the picture is the interplay between the elegant lady — 
                            the owner of a fashion shop in Paris — and the gentlemen turned in her direction. 
                            He seems rather small due to the way he is bending over and brushes against the upper 
                            edge of the picture, while the feminine beauty with the effortless noblesse of her extended 
                            posture occupies a large part of the picture space. Despite their being separated by the 
                            back of the seat — with its own graphic appeal by virtue of its transparency — the understated 
                            focal point of this rich conservatory scene with all its plant forms and subtle colours is the 
                            hands approaching each other. Manet’s paintings are fascinating for a variety of reasons: 
                            a palette of colours that is subtle yet not without the tension of contrast, plus subject 
                            matter that is free from literary or symbolic content. This is painting at its highest level, 
                            drawing on an uncommonly fertile imagination, on the constant awareness of visual phenomena, 
                            and on a gift for laconic observation that translates every sight into a subtly mediated 
                            experience for the eyes. Particularly in the compositions with two or more figures, there are 
                            also extremely skilfully dramatized scenes with psychologically intriguing configurations of
                            actors or often of silent players, wordless and motionless like the different elements in a still life.
                        </FreeTextAnnotation>
                        <StructuredAnnotation>
                            <Name>	
                                <Name>In the Conservatory</Name>
                            </Name>
                            <Creator>
                                <Name>Edouard Manet</Name>	
                            </Creator>
                            <Period>
                                <Name>Impressionism</Name>          						
                            </Period>
                            <Technique>
                                <Name>Oil painting</Name>
                            </Technique>
                            <Materials>
                                <Name>Oil on canvas</Name>
                            </Materials>
                            <Height>
                                <Name></Name>
                            </Height>
                            <Width>
                                <Name></Name>
                            </Width>
                            <Date>
                                <Name>
                                    1879
                                </Name>
                            </Date>
                            <Actor>
                                <Name>Jules Guillemet, M-me Jules Guillemet, Johann Georges Otto Rosen</Name>          
                            </Actor>
                            <Location>
                                <Name>Stockholm, Sweden</Name> 
                            </Location>
                            <Activity>
                                <Name>Couple in conservatory</Name>
                            </Activity>
                            <Theme>
                                <Name>Impressionism, Conservatory, Relationships, Color, Plants</Name>
                            </Theme>
                            <Concept>
                                <Name>Man, Woman, Bench, Urn, Flowersm Plants, Conservatory, Dress, Suit, Umbrella</Name>
                            </Concept>															            
                        </StructuredAnnotation>
                    </TextAnnotation>
                    <Semantic>
                        <Label>
                            <Name />
                        </Label>
                        <SemanticBase xsi:type="AgentObjectType" id="id_1">
                            <Label>
                                <Name></Name>
                            </Label>
                            <Agent xsi:type="PersonType">
                                <Name>
                                    <GivenName>Edouard</GivenName>
                                    <FamilyName>Manet</FamilyName>
                                </Name>
                            </Agent>
                        </SemanticBase>
                        <SemanticBase xsi:type="SemanticTimeType" id="id_2">
                            <Label>
                                <Name>1879</Name>
                            </Label>
                            <Definition>
                                <FreeTextAnnotation>This semantic time defines the period of 1879</FreeTextAnnotation>
                            </Definition>
                            <Time>
                                <TimePoint>2004-07-01T12:00</TimePoint>
                            </Time>
                        </SemanticBase>
                        <SemanticBase xsi:type="EventType" id="id_3">
                            <Label>
                                <Name>A scene depicting a couple in a conservatory</Name>
                            </Label>
                            <Definition>
                                <FreeTextAnnotation></FreeTextAnnotation>
                            </Definition>
                            <Event>
                                <Label>
                                    <Name>Portrait</Name>
                                </Label>
                                <SemanticPlace>
                                    <Label>
                                        <Name>
                                           Sweden
                                        </Name>
                                    </Label>
                                </SemanticPlace>
                                <SemanticTime>
                                    <Label>
                                        <Name>Time of the event</Name>
                                    </Label>
                                    <Time>
                                        <TimePoint>1879-10-08T10:50</TimePoint>
                                    </Time>
                                </SemanticTime>
                            </Event>
                        </SemanticBase>
                        <SemanticBase xsi:type="EventType" id="id_4">
                            <Label>
                                <Name>Composition scene</Name>
                            </Label>
                            <Definition>
                                <FreeTextAnnotation>Édouard Manet was one of the most important and controversial 
                                French painters of the 19th century, whose works sometimes scandalized Parisian 
                                society and became a great inspiration for the Impressionists. In 1845 he took part 
                                in a special course of drawing and met Antonin Proust who later became the Minister 
                                of Fine Arts. From 1850–56 Manet was an apprentice under the history painter Thomas 
                                Couture and copied the old masters in the Louvre. In 1853 he travelled to Germany, 
                                Italy and the Netherlands where he was influenced by Dutch artists such as Frans Hals 
                                as well as by Spanish painters like Diego Velázquez and Francisco Josè de Goya. 
                                In 1856 he opened his own studio. During his early years his style was characterized 
                                by simplified details and the realism of his day. His main subjects were people, for 
                                example in cafés or ballet scenes, humble persons such as beggars or gypsies and scenes 
                                of daily life. Rather less frequently, he also painted religious, mythological or historical 
                                themes. His friends included several Impressionist painters such as Claude Monet, 
                                Pierre-Auguste Renoir or Paul Cézanne. Manet became famous for artworks like 'Le déjeuner 
                                sur l’herbe' (1862), 'Olympia' (1863) 'A Bar at the Folies-Bergère' (1882) and 'The Café Concert' (1878).
                                </FreeTextAnnotation>
                            </Definition>
                            </SemanticBase>
                            <SemanticBase xsi:type="ConceptType" id="id_6">
                                <Label>
                                    <Name>Relationships, Tense, Couples, Conservatory</Name>
                                </Label>
                                <Agent xsi:type="AbstractType">
                                    <Name>
                                        <GivenName>Edouard</GivenName>
                                        <FamilyName>Manet</FamilyName>
                                    </Name>
                                </Agent>
                            </SemanticBase>
                            <Graph>
                                <Relation type="urn:mpeg:mpeg7:cs:SemanticRelationCS:2001:exemplifies" source="#id_3" target="#id_2" />
                                <Relation type="urn:mpeg:mpeg7:cs:SemanticRelationCS:2001:appearsIn" source="#id_2" target="#id_1" />
                            </Graph>
                        </Semantic>        
                    </Image>
                </MultimediaContent>
            </Description>
        </Mpeg7>

