<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Mpeg7 xmlns="urn:mpeg:mpeg7:schema:2001" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <DescriptionMetadata>
        <Version>5.0</Version>
        <Comment>
            <FreeTextAnnotation />
        </Comment>
        <Creator>
            <Role href="creatorCS">
                <Name>Creator</Name>
            </Role>
            <Agent xsi:type="PersonType">
                <Name>
                    <FamilyName>Olav</FamilyName>
                    <GivenName>Løne</GivenName> 
                </Name>
            </Agent>
        </Creator>
        <CreationTime>2012-04-19T17:13</CreationTime>
        <Instrument>
            <Tool>
                <Name>Aardvark v0.56</Name>
            </Tool>
        </Instrument>
    </DescriptionMetadata>
    <Description xsi:type="ContentEntityType">
        <MultimediaContent xsi:type="ImageType">
            <Image>
                <MediaInformation>
                    <MediaProfile master="true">
                        <MediaFormat>
                            <Content href="image" />
                            <FileFormat href="urn:mpeg:MPEG7FileFormatCS:1">
                                <Name>JPEG</Name>
                            </FileFormat>
                            <VisualCoding>
                                <Format href="urn:mpeg:MPEG7FileFormatCS:1" colorDomain="color">
                                    <Name>JPEG</Name>
                                </Format>
                                <Pixel bitsPer="24" />
                                <Frame width="2592" height="1944" />
                            </VisualCoding>
                        </MediaFormat>
                        <MediaInstance>
                            <InstanceIdentifier />
                            <MediaLocator>
                                <MediaUri>C:\Users\Olav\Documents\Oppgaave\Bilete\Mill on the Couleuvre at Pontoise.jpg</MediaUri>
                            </MediaLocator>
                        </MediaInstance>
                    </MediaProfile>
                    <MediaProfile>
                        <MediaFormat>
                            <Content href="image" />
                            <FileFormat href="urn:mpeg:MPEG7FileFormatCS:1">
                                <Name>JPEG</Name>
                            </FileFormat>
                            <VisualCoding>
                                <Format href="urn:mpeg:MPEG7FileFormatCS:1" colorDomain="color">
                                    <Name>JPEG</Name>
                                </Format>
                                <Pixel bitsPer="24" />
                                <Frame width="120" height="120" />
                            </VisualCoding>
                        </MediaFormat>
                        <MediaInstance>
                            <InstanceIdentifier />
                            <MediaLocator>
                                <MediaUri>C:\Users\Olav\Documents\Oppgaave\Bilete\Mill on the Couleuvre at Pontoise.jpg</MediaUri>
                            </MediaLocator>
                        </MediaInstance>
                    </MediaProfile>
                </MediaInformation>
                <CreationInformation>
                    <Creation>
                        <Title>Creation information</Title>
                        <Creator>
                            <Role href="creatorCS">
                                <Name>Creator</Name>
                            </Role>
                            <Agent xsi:type="PersonType">
                                <Name>
                                    <FamilyName>vCézanne</FamilyName>
                                    <GivenName>Paul</GivenName>
                                </Name>
                            </Agent>
                        </Creator>
                        <CreationCoordinates>
                            <Date>
                                <TimePoint>2008-05-28T22:02:13</TimePoint>
                            </Date>
                        </CreationCoordinates>
                        </Creation>
                    </CreationInformation>  
                    <TextAnnotation>
                        <FreeTextAnnotation>  
                        Cézanne’s art was still highly controversial when the Nationalgalerie purchased 
                        this painting: it was only two years previously that the French government had 
                        accepted two of his works as part of the Caillebotte donation, but had rejected 
                        another three. For a long time, Cézanne commuted between his place of birth, 
                        Aix-en-Provence, and Paris, although he also stayed in various towns of the Ile-de-France. 
                        Camille Pissarro lived in Pontoise northwest of Paris. Cézanne paid him several visits 
                        there (the first in 1872, the last from May to October of 1881), and their work together 
                        encouraged him in the direction of light, impressionistic colours: “We perhaps all go 
                        back to Pissarro,” he later said. The older painter also led him to that clarity and 
                        calm that pervade the painting of the mill, and which are achieved despite extraordinary 
                        accuracy in his portrayal of the motif; this is clear from old pictures showing the 
                        Moulin des Etannets on the rue des Deux Ponts, one of many mills in that area that 
                        depended on the corn trade for its existence. The flat white houses in the background 
                        create a sober effect. At the same time, there is a geometric order that takes in
                        the whole picture plane. The composition is governed by strict horizontals and verticals 
                        cutting across each other. Despite interruptions, these apparently run as parallels 
                        throughout the whole picture; closer examination, however, shows that in the lower 
                        half of the picture, that is to say in the foreground, they slope away increasingly 
                        into diagonals. The colours range through shades of green to airy blue and ocher. 
                        Since each brushstroke is independent — whether short and straight or curved or 
                        even curled — the paint does not entirely cover the painting’s ground, thus incorporating 
                        its pale, immaterial quality.
                           </FreeTextAnnotation>
                        <StructuredAnnotation>
                            <Name>	
                                <Name>Mill on the Couleuvre at Pontoise</Name>
                            </Name>
                            <Creator>
                                <Name>Paul Cézanne</Name>	
                            </Creator>
                            <Period>
                                <Name>Impressionism</Name>          						
                            </Period>
                            <Technique>
                                <Name>Oil painting</Name>
                            </Technique>
                            <Materials>
                                <Name>Oil on canvas</Name>
                            </Materials>
                            <Height>
                                <Name>73</Name>
                            </Height>
                            <Width>
                                <Name>91</Name>
                            </Width>
                            <Date>
                                <Name>
                                    1881
                                </Name>
                            </Date>
                            <Actor>
                                <Name>Mill</Name>          
                            </Actor>
                            <Location>
                                    <Name>Pontoise, France </Name> 
                            </Location>
                            <Activity>
                                <Name>Mill</Name>
                            </Activity>
                            <Theme>
                                <Name>Impressionism, Mill, Light, clouds, cold light, Calm, Stillness, 
                                Geometry, Strict, Calm, Composition, Late 19th century</Name>
                            </Theme>
                            <Concept>
                                <Name>Outdoors</Name>
                            </Concept>															            
                        </StructuredAnnotation>
                    </TextAnnotation>
                    <Semantic>
                        <Label>
                            <Name />
                        </Label>
                        <SemanticBase xsi:type="AgentObjectType" id="id_1">
                            <Label>
                                <Name></Name>
                            </Label>
                            <Agent xsi:type="PersonType">
                                <Name>
                                    <GivenName>Paul</GivenName>
                                    <FamilyName>Cézanne</FamilyName>
                                </Name>
                            </Agent>
                        </SemanticBase>
                        <SemanticBase xsi:type="SemanticTimeType" id="id_2">
                            <Label>
                                <Name>1774</Name>
                            </Label>
                            <Definition>
                                <FreeTextAnnotation>This semantic time defines the period of 1881</FreeTextAnnotation>
                            </Definition>
                            <Time>
                                <TimePoint>2004-07-01T12:00</TimePoint>
                            </Time>
                        </SemanticBase>
                        <SemanticBase xsi:type="EventType" id="id_3">
                            <Label>
                                <Name>A outdoor landscape scene depicting an old mill ouside of Paris</Name>
                            </Label>
                            <Definition>
                                <FreeTextAnnotation></FreeTextAnnotation>
                            </Definition>
                            <Event>
                                <Label>
                                    <Name>Landscape scene</Name>
                                </Label>
                                <SemanticPlace>
                                    <Label>
                                        <Name>
                                            Pontoise, France
                                        </Name>
                                    </Label>
                                </SemanticPlace>
                                <SemanticTime>
                                    <Label>
                                        <Name>Time of the event</Name>
                                    </Label>
                                    <Time>
                                        <TimePoint>1881-10-08T10:50</TimePoint>
                                    </Time>
                                </SemanticTime>
                            </Event>
                        </SemanticBase>
                        <SemanticBase xsi:type="EventType" id="id_4">
                            <Label>
                                <Name>Landscape Scene</Name>
                            </Label>
                            <Definition>
                                <FreeTextAnnotation> 
                                Paul Cézanne was a French artist and Post-Impressionist painter. 
                                Following the wish of his father, a banker, he began studying law in 1859, 
                                while simultaneously taking evening classes at the local drawing school. 
                                His teacher was the painter Jospeh Gibert. His early works demonstrate the 
                                influence of Romanticism which was to disappear later on. In 1861 he moved 
                                to Paris where he studied at the Académie Suisse, specializing mainly in 
                                drawings of nudes. Parallel to this, he copied the works of old masters in 
                                the Louvre such as those by Michelangelo, Rubens and Titian. In 1872 he 
                                followed his friend Pissarro to Pontoise where he was taught by him. As a 
                                result of his influence, Cézanne’s initial preference for dark colours ended 
                                and his gaze turned towards finding new ways of depicting outdoor light, a 
                                core interest of Impressionism. Two years later he took part in an exhibition 
                                of young Parisian artists who felt disgruntled by the Salon de Paris and who 
                                later became known as the Impressionists. From 1890 until his death he withdrew 
                                into his painting, at times leading a recluse-like existence. During this time 
                                however, his works became famous, gaining him respect from a new generation of 
                                artists. Cézanne formed a bridge from the Impressionism of the late 19th century 
                                to the Cubism of the early 20th century. He was a master of colour and composition 
                                and a forerunner of abstraction. In contrast to most artists of his time, he was 
                                deeply influenced by Gustave Courbet and Eugène Delacroix and their realistic 
                                approach to the painted subject. He was the first artist to depict objects broken 
                                down in their simple geometric forms. Cézanne is well known for compositions like 
                                'Mill On The Couleuvre near Pontoise' (1881), 'The Card Players' (1892) and 
                                'Still Life with a Curtain' (1895).
                                </FreeTextAnnotation>
                            </Definition>
                            </SemanticBase>
                            <SemanticBase xsi:type="ConceptType" id="id_6">
                                <Label>
                                    <Name>Light, Landscape, Buildings, Calm</Name>
                                </Label>
                                <Agent xsi:type="AbstractType">
                                    <Name>
                                        <GivenName>Paul</GivenName>
                                        <FamilyName>Cézanne</FamilyName>
                                    </Name>
                                </Agent>
                            </SemanticBase>
                            <Graph>
                                <Relation type="urn:mpeg:mpeg7:cs:SemanticRelationCS:2001:exemplifies" source="#id_3" target="#id_2" />
                                <Relation type="urn:mpeg:mpeg7:cs:SemanticRelationCS:2001:appearsIn" source="#id_2" target="#id_1" />
                            </Graph>
                        </Semantic>        
                    </Image>
                </MultimediaContent>
            </Description>
        </Mpeg7>

