<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Mpeg7 xmlns="urn:mpeg:mpeg7:schema:2001" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <DescriptionMetadata>
        <Version>5.0</Version>
        <Comment>
            <FreeTextAnnotation />
        </Comment>
        <Creator>
            <Role href="creatorCS">
                <Name>Creator</Name>
            </Role>
            <Agent xsi:type="PersonType">
                <Name>
                    <FamilyName>Olav</FamilyName>
                    <GivenName>Løne</GivenName> 
                </Name>
            </Agent>
        </Creator>
        <CreationTime>2012-04-19T17:13</CreationTime>
        <Instrument>
            <Tool>
                <Name>Aardvark v0.56</Name>
            </Tool>
        </Instrument>
    </DescriptionMetadata>
    <Description xsi:type="ContentEntityType">
        <MultimediaContent xsi:type="ImageType">
            <Image>
                <MediaInformation>
                    <MediaProfile master="true">
                        <MediaFormat>
                            <Content href="image" />
                            <FileFormat href="urn:mpeg:MPEG7FileFormatCS:1">
                                <Name>JPEG</Name>
                            </FileFormat>
                            <VisualCoding>
                                <Format href="urn:mpeg:MPEG7FileFormatCS:1" colorDomain="color">
                                    <Name>JPEG</Name>
                                </Format>
                                <Pixel bitsPer="24" />
                                <Frame width="2592" height="1944" />
                            </VisualCoding>
                        </MediaFormat>
                        <MediaInstance>
                            <InstanceIdentifier />
                            <MediaLocator>
                                <MediaUri>C:\Users\Olav\Documents\Oppgaave\Bilete\Moonrise over the Sea.jpg</MediaUri>
                            </MediaLocator>
                        </MediaInstance>
                    </MediaProfile>
                    <MediaProfile>
                        <MediaFormat>
                            <Content href="image" />
                            <FileFormat href="urn:mpeg:MPEG7FileFormatCS:1">
                                <Name>JPEG</Name>
                            </FileFormat>
                            <VisualCoding>
                                <Format href="urn:mpeg:MPEG7FileFormatCS:1" colorDomain="color">
                                    <Name>JPEG</Name>
                                </Format>
                                <Pixel bitsPer="24" />
                                <Frame width="120" height="120" />
                            </VisualCoding>
                        </MediaFormat>
                        <MediaInstance>
                            <InstanceIdentifier />
                            <MediaLocator>
                                <MediaUri>C:\Users\Olav\Documents\Oppgaave\Bilete\Moonrise over the Sea.jpg</MediaUri>
                            </MediaLocator>
                        </MediaInstance>
                    </MediaProfile>
                </MediaInformation>
                <CreationInformation>
                    <Creation>
                        <Title>Creation information</Title>
                        <Creator>
                            <Role href="creatorCS">
                                <Name>Creator</Name>
                            </Role>
                            <Agent xsi:type="PersonType">
                                <Name>
                                    <FamilyName>Friedrich</FamilyName>
                                    <GivenName>Caspar David</GivenName>
                                </Name>
                            </Agent>
                        </Creator>
                        <CreationCoordinates>
                            <Date>
                                <TimePoint>2008-05-28T22:02:13</TimePoint>
                            </Date>
                        </CreationCoordinates>
                        </Creation>
                    </CreationInformation>  
                    <TextAnnotation>
                        <FreeTextAnnotation>
                           Like its companion piece, the evening picture of the diptych was painted in 1822. 
                           In Moonrise on the Seashore Friedrich took up one of his favorite themes. In the 
                           reflected light of the night sky, it is as though the surface of the water begins 
                           to glow all of its own accord, taking up the light of heaven, as it were. Clouds 
                           have come up and the round shape of the full moon is half hidden behind the banks 
                           of cloud at the horizon. This means that the moonlight does not fall evenly but 
                           seems to be breaking out of a gateway in the clouds, creating a magical play of 
                           light. Complementary colours, ranging from golden to whitish yellow, violet and blue, 
                           define the contrasts of light and shade. There is a sense of the magnitude and unity 
                           of the universe. Moved by this wonder of nature, three people sit on rounded rocks 
                           near the shore, and their dark silhouettes heighten the effect of the gleaming light 
                           of the sky and the sea. Two sailing ships pursue a ghostly course across the water. 
                           The sublime drama with the moon as the symbol of hope is imbued with a quality of 
                           unearthly beauty.
                         </FreeTextAnnotation>
                        <StructuredAnnotation>
                            <Name>	
                                <Name>Moonrise over the Sea</Name>
                            </Name>
                            <Creator>
                                <Name>Caspar David Friedrich</Name>	
                            </Creator>
                            <Period>
                                <Name>Romanticisism</Name>          						
                            </Period>
                            <Technique>
                                <Name>Oil painting</Name>
                            </Technique>
                            <Materials>
                                <Name>Oil on canvas</Name>
                            </Materials>
                            <Height>
                                <Name></Name>
                            </Height>
                            <Width>
                                <Name></Name>
                            </Width>
                            <Date>
                                <Name>
                                    1822
                                </Name>
                            </Date>
                            <Actor>
                                <Name>A familiy</Name>          
                            </Actor>
                            <Location>
                                    <Name>Unknown</Name> 
                            </Location>
                            <Activity>
                                <Name>Watching the moonrise</Name>
                            </Activity>
                            <Theme>
                                <Name>Romatisicm, Early 19th century, Germany, Hope, Beauty, Rebirth, Moonlight, Dusk, Night, Sea, Nautic, Clouds, Ghostly</Name>
                            </Theme>
                            <Concept>
                                <Name>Boats, Ships, Women, Men, Clouds, Moon, Beach, Sea, Rocks</Name>
                            </Concept>															            
                        </StructuredAnnotation>
                    </TextAnnotation>
                    <Semantic>
                        <Label>
                            <Name />
                        </Label>
                        <SemanticBase xsi:type="AgentObjectType" id="id_1">
                            <Label>
                                <Name></Name>
                            </Label>
                            <Agent xsi:type="PersonType">
                                <Name>
                                    <GivenName>Caspar David</GivenName>
                                    <FamilyName>Friedrich</FamilyName>
                                </Name>
                            </Agent>
                        </SemanticBase>
                        <SemanticBase xsi:type="SemanticTimeType" id="id_2">
                            <Label>
                                <Name>1822</Name>
                            </Label>
                            <Definition>
                                <FreeTextAnnotation>This semantic time defines the period of 1822</FreeTextAnnotation>
                            </Definition>
                            <Time>
                                <TimePoint>1822-07-01T12:00</TimePoint>
                            </Time>
                        </SemanticBase>
                        <SemanticBase xsi:type="EventType" id="id_3">
                            <Label>
                                <Name>A landscape scene depicting a family looking at the moonrise by the sea at dusk</Name>
                            </Label>
                            <Definition>
                                <FreeTextAnnotation></FreeTextAnnotation>
                            </Definition>
                            <Event>
                                <Label>
                                    <Name>Landscape scene</Name>
                                </Label>
                                <SemanticPlace>
                                    <Label>
                                        <Name>
                                            Germany
                                        </Name>
                                    </Label>
                                </SemanticPlace>
                                <SemanticTime>
                                    <Label>
                                        <Name>Time of the event</Name>
                                    </Label>
                                    <Time>
                                        <TimePoint>11822-10-08T10:50</TimePoint>
                                    </Time>
                                </SemanticTime>
                            </Event>
                        </SemanticBase>
                        <SemanticBase xsi:type="EventType" id="id_4">
                            <Label>
                                <Name>Outdoor Scene</Name>
                            </Label>
                            <Definition>
                                <FreeTextAnnotation>
                                    Caspar David Friedrich was the most important German painter and draughtsman of 
                                    the early Romantic period. He started his artistic training in 1790 when he became 
                                    a private student of Johann Gottfried Quistorp in Greifswald. In 1794 he entered 
                                    the Academy of Copenhagen where he formed his style copying antique sculptures. 
                                    During this period he served as an apprentice under Christian August Lorentzen and 
                                    Jens Juel. These artists were exponents of the Sturm und Drang movement which was 
                                    characterized by individual subjectivity and heightened emotionality. Friedrich 
                                    settled in Dresden, where he worked in printmaking with etchings and layouts for 
                                    woodcuts, later turning to watercolours, ink and sepias. From 1801 he made frequent
                                    trips to the Baltic coast and various German mountains, drawing inspiration for a 
                                    number of landscape paintings which soon became his favourite subject. Friedrich won 
                                    a competition, set up by Johann Wolfgang von Goethe in Weimar in 1805, with his 
                                    sepia drawings 'Procession at Dawn' and 'Fisher-Folk by the Sea'. He also gained 
                                    recognition for being the first artist to depict a landscape in an altarpiece, with 
                                    'The Cross in the Mountains' (1807) becoming one of his most important artworks. 
                                    In 1810 he was appointed a member of the Berlin Academy. He was held in high esteem 
                                    even as far away as Russia, by the Grand Duke Nikolai Pavlovich and the tutor to 
                                    Alexander II, Vasily Zhukovsky, who supported him by purchasing works himself and 
                                    recommending him to other nobles. Friedrich’s prestige decreased over the last years 
                                    of his life when he lived in relative poverty, making him dependent on the charity 
                                    of friends. Among them were a number of important artists such as Philipp Otto Runge, 
                                    Georg Friedrich Kersting and Christian Dahl. Friedrich’s compositions are characterized 
                                    by metaphysical transcendence. His main subjects were landscapes and he forged a new 
                                    way of depicting nature: often using a ‘back figure’, whereby a figure contemplating 
                                    the view is seen from behind. His landscapes widely present religious topics, while 
                                    his winter landscapes show a raw and powerful side to nature of a kind never depicted 
                                    before. It is purely thanks to Friedrich and other Romantic painters that the genre of 
                                    landscape painting holds such an important status within Western art as a whole. Among 
                                    his most famous works are 'The Wanderer above the Mists' (1818), 'Chalk Cliffs on Rügen' 
                                    (1818), 'The Abbey in the Oakwood' (1808–10) and 'Man and Woman Contemplating the Moon' 
                                    (1830–35).
                                </FreeTextAnnotation>
                            </Definition>
                            </SemanticBase>
                            <SemanticBase xsi:type="ConceptType" id="id_6">
                                <Label>
                                    <Name>Hope, Beauty, Calm, Moonlight</Name>
                                </Label>
                                <Agent xsi:type="AbstractType">
                                    <Name>
                                        <GivenName>Caspar David</GivenName>
                                        <FamilyName>Friedrich</FamilyName>
                                    </Name>
                                </Agent>
                            </SemanticBase>
                            <Graph>
                                <Relation type="urn:mpeg:mpeg7:cs:SemanticRelationCS:2001:exemplifies" source="#id_3" target="#id_2" />
                                <Relation type="urn:mpeg:mpeg7:cs:SemanticRelationCS:2001:appearsIn" source="#id_2" target="#id_1" />
                            </Graph>
                        </Semantic>        
                    </Image>
                </MultimediaContent>
            </Description>
        </Mpeg7>

